{
    "id": "95e46be0c82b45a1854010617e9e9770",
    "title": "Phrasal Verbs With Do and Make",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "We cannot ..................... without food or water.",
            "description": "To do without something is to manage without that.",
            "answers": [
                "do",
                "with",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "76e0780518fe409789cf40190b762cc0"
        },
        {
            "question": "Child marriage is a bad custom and should be ………………. with.",
            "description": "To do away with a custom is to abolish it.",
            "answers": [
                "done off",
                "done away",
                "done up"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9fdaa5bfd60f46a2b5a97de739e638bf"
        },
        {
            "question": "His elder brother did him ………………… his rightful inheritance.",
            "description": "To do someone out of something is to prevent them from having it.",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "of",
                "out of"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "d628f5cbdd5242078baa082e3d57ccc5"
        },
        {
            "question": "We are ……………….. the kitchen on the weekend.",
            "description": "To do up the kitchen is to renovate it.",
            "answers": [
                "making up",
                "doing up",
                "doing out"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "87f177189d5940209c60e7428dfd624c"
        },
        {
            "question": "As soon as the thief saw the dog rushing towards him, he ……………… the gate.",
            "description": "To make for the door is to move in the direction of the door.",
            "answers": [
                "made out",
                "made for",
                "made off"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "dc55f2cb805b4f9e9cd32c8e7f676879"
        },
        {
            "question": "What do you make ……………….. her new boyfriend?",
            "description": "Make of means think of.",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "of",
                "off",
                "up"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "117e3e51209043fca9c3adfd38a3c8e0"
        },
        {
            "question": "He made ……………….. as soon as he heard that his mother had fallen ill.",
            "description": "To make off is to leave hurriedly.",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "off",
                "out"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "652aec2a3767416091977e420a83aced"
        },
        {
            "question": "The superb food at the restaurant made ………………… the bad service.",
            "description": "To make up for something is to compensate for it. ",
            "answers": [
                "out for",
                "for",
                "up for"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "1c3cd56b4d8c4a33b05c430ba07904f3"
        },
        {
            "question": "The boy made ……………….. to his mother until she allowed him to go to the movies.",
            "description": "To make up to somebody is to be nice to them with objective of getting something.",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "out",
                "off"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "36708fb7ea304103a3f80132122f2f7f"
        },
        {
            "question": "The human body is ………………… of the five elements.",
            "description": "Make up means compose or constitute.",
            "answers": [
                "made out",
                "made up",
                "made off"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7045394bf1c943c5a475e2b72cc7887b"
        },
        {
            "question": "I find it rather difficult to make him ……………..",
            "description": "To make somebody out is to understand them.",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "out",
                "off"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "07a0333743e64fe1a4b95aa3bfafe587"
        },
        {
            "question": "I always fight with my husband but we …………………. soon after.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "do up",
                "make off",
                "make up"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "0a4f913cfee74e70a2f3a915dc3613e3"
        }
    ]
}